

CHARLENE BACLAYON

SEO LINK BUILDING SPECIALIST

PERSONAL PROFILE

I've been a Virtual Assistant for 10 years providing an excellent work. Excellent problem solver, have the Can-do attitude and detail oriented. Extremely motivated to constantly develop my skills and grow professionally. I am confident in my ability to come up with interesting ideas.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- Social Media Marketing | Social Media Management
- Email Management | Calendar Management
- Video Editing | Photo Editing | Filmora | Data Mining | Email Mining
- Research | Data Entry
- Spreadsheet | Presentation | Word Processing
- Skype | Google Talk | Google Hangouts | LogMeIn | TeamViewer
- Dropbox | Box | Google Drive | MeetEdgar | Trello | Slack | Google Apps | Google Maps | Google Analytics
- TimeDoctor | Screenshot Monitor | Hubstaff | Clockify
- Adobe Photoshop | Adobe InDesign | Hootsuite | Buffer | Tailwind

WORK EXPERIENCE

VIRTUAL F1

General Admin VA, June 2015 - Jan. 2017

NATISHA WILLIS, LLC

Social Media Manager | Transcriptionist | Graphic Designer, Feb.2017 - Aug. 2017 KIM SUTTON

Social Media Manager | Transcriptionist | Virtual Assistant, Apr.2017 - June. 2017

PALLADOUS MARKETING

Data Researcher | Outreacher, June. 2017 - Oct. 2017

SKYROCKET

Outreacher | Link Building | Content Promotion, Aug. 2017 - Jan. 2019

PROPULSE VIDEO

Linkedin Specialist | Lead Generation, Feb. 2018 - Aug. 2018

SHARPROCKET

Outreacher | Link Building, June. 2018 - Feb, 2020

JASON TURTOGA

Outreacher | Link Building | Contact Finding, Aug. 2019 - Present

GET IN CONTACT

Mobile: +63 907 156 1391 charlenebaclayon14@gmail.com Skype: charlenebaclayon Purok Dangit, San Isidro, Padada Dayao Del Sur

EDUCATION HISTORY

MINTECH

Information Communication Technology, 2011

SOUTHEASTERN OF PADADA, INC

Bachelor of Secondary Education, Major in English, 2021-2022